appveyor.com 2019-08-25

# Privacy Policy | AppVeyor

The purpose of this Policy is to make visitors to this website aware of how AppVeyor Systems Inc. (" **AppVeyor** ") collects, uses, manages and discloses Personal Information.

This Policy explains generally AppVeyor's Personal Information practices, but in all respects this Policy and the application of our practices will be subject to and in accordance with the provisions of applicable privacy protection laws.

  1. Interpretation
    1.  **Definitions**. Where used in this Policy, each of the following words and phrases shall have the meanings set out below:
      1. " **AppVeyor On-Premise** " means the downloadable program created by AppVeyor for building, testing, and deploying applications;
      2. " **End User License Agreement** " means AppVeyor's End User License Agreement available at appveyor.com/eula;
      3. " **Microsoft** " means Microsoft Corporation, including its affiliated entities and operations;
      4. " **Personal Information** " means information about an identifiable individual, and includes things such as gender, age, ethnicity and financial information, health information, consumer preference information, user profiles and identification numbers;
      5. " **Privacy Officer** " refers to the individual or individuals that are accountable for AppVeyor's compliance with these principles, and to any policies adopted by AppVeyor thereto;
      6. " **Privacy Policy** " or " **Policy** " is AppVeyor's Policy set out herein which makes visitors to the Site aware of how AppVeyor collects, uses, manages and discloses Personal Information;
      7. " **Services** " means the services AppVeyor provides the User on the Site or which are available through the Site, including but not limited to the provision of developer tools for building, testing, deploying and managing web applications including any support services and other business applications and online services that may be provided by AppVeyor;
      8. " **Site** " means AppVeyor's website located at [www.appveyor.com](https://www.appveyor.com/), including all services, tools, forums and other content and information made available on the website;
      9. " **Terms of Service Agreement** " means AppVeyor's Terms of Service Agreement available at appveyor.com/terms-of-service, as updated from time to time; and
      10. " **User** " or " **you** " means any individual, on their own behalf or on behalf of an entity whom they are authorized to represent which has entered into the Terms of Service Agreement and/or the End User License Agreement in connection with the Site and/or Services.
  2. Knowledge and Consent
    1. By using the Site and/or our Services, you are consenting to the collection and use of information as described in this Policy. AppVeyor may amend this Policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your Personal Information we will notify you by posting an announcement on the Site. By continuing to use the Site and/or the Services after any such changes are posted, you are consenting to those changes.
  3. Collection of Information
    1. AppVeyor collects personal information in three ways.
      1. First, our website uses cookies. These cookies are automatically placed on your computer or mobile device that uniquely identify your browser or device. We use cookies to personalize content and ads, to provide social media features and to analyse our traffic. We also share information about your use of our site with our social media, advertising and analytics partners who may combine it with other information that you’ve provided to them or that they’ve collected from your use of their services. By using our website, you are consenting to our use of cookies.
      2. Second, we collect personal information that you provide to us through our Site. If you create an account with us, the personal information that you provide is used for the purposes set forth in Section 3.2, below. If, when you create an account, you use the option to sign up with you existing developer account, we may receive additional personal information about you depending on your settings with such developer account. If we receive information additional to your name and email address, you expressly consent to us receiving and processing that information for the purposes set forth in Section 3.2, below. If you also consent to receiving emails from us, either when you create an account or at any other time, we will use the personal information you provide for the purposes set forth in Section 3.3, below.
      3. Finally, if a user creates an account, that person is the “Account Owner.” The Account Owner may invite other users (each, an “Invited Users”) to the same account by entering the email address of the Invited User as indicated in our Services. We use such email address solely for the purposes of delivering the invitation. No other personal information is collected about the Invited User unless the invitation is accepted and the Terms and Conditions of this Privacy Policy are consented to. We keep the email address of the Invited User until the earliest of one of the following: (i) the Owner deletes the invitation; (ii) the account for which the invitation is deleted; or (iii) the Invited User sends us a request to delete the invitation (such requests can be made in writing to team@appveyor.com.
    2. We collect the names and emails addresses and IP addresses of all account Users, and for all Users of the free version of Appeyor On-Premise, which is available for download and use without an account. If you sign up for a paid account, we will also collect your billing information (name and address). We use encrypted technology to process your payment through our third party payment processor (Stripe), which means we never have access to your credit card details. Occasionally, we may request additional personal information for the specific purpose of providing Services that require that information. If you are the Owner of an account, then you can make a written request to have your account deleted by writing to team@appveyor.com. We will delete your account within 30 days, along with the personal information of any User associated with that account. If you are not the account Owner, you can make a request to the Owner of the account to remove you from the account. You can also write us directly at team@appveyor.com to request removal. When you are removed, all of your personal information associated with that account is also deleted. Note that deleting your account or removing yourself from an account does not remove you from our mailing list, but you can unsubscribe from our mailing list at any time. We use the personal information provided through your account to administer our Services to you, as more specifically set forth below:
      1. to administer and build your AppVeyor account;
      2. to communicate with you for the purpose of informing you of changes or additions to our Services, or of the availability of any of our products or services;
      3. to communicate with you for the purpose of sending build/deployment notifications, newsletters, technical updates and other communications;
      4. to provide the Services to you, including when third-parties may be engaged in the provision of the Services;
      5. to notify you (on an opt-in basis) of new products and services offered by ourselves that we believe may be of interest to you;
      6. to provide you with system notifications;
      7. to gather information about how you are use our Site and Services and your preferences, and to customize our offers and Services to you;
      8. to enforce this Policy, the End User License Agreement, and the Terms of Service Agreement;
      9. to respond to claims that any content violates the rights of any third-parties;
      10. to respond to your request for customer service;
      11. to protect the rights, property or personal safety of AppVeyor, its users and the public; or
      12. as required or authorized by law.

You have the right to object to your information being processed as set forth in section 3.2(g), by sending your objection to privacy@appveyor.com. To the extent that any of your information is processed for direct marketing purpose, we will cease such processing after receiving your objection. For processing unrelated to direct marketing purposes, we will evaluate your objection and respond within 30 days. Please bear in mind that if you object, this may affect our ability to carry out tasks above for your benefit.

    3. If you consent to receiving emails from AppVeyor that are unrelated to the Services provided through your account, we will store your name and email address, and send you emails through our email service provider, Mailgun. You may unsubscribe from our emails at any time by clicking the "Unsubscribe" link at the bottom of any of our emails, or by modifying your profile in your account. Mailgun maintains a list of all of our users who have unsubscribed from our emails. If you would like your name and email address deleted from this list, you can contact us at [privacy@appveyor.com](mailto:privacy@appveyor.com) to make that request. For so long as you are a subscriber to our emails, we will use your name and email to for the purposes set forth below:
      1. to communicate with you for the purpose of informing you of changes or additions to our services, or of the availability of any of our products or services;
      2. to communicate with you for the purpose of sending build/deployment notifications, newsletters, technical updates and other communications;
      3. to notify you (on an opt-in basis) of new products and services offered by ourselves that we believe may be of interest to you;
      4. to provide you with system notifications;
      5. to enforce this Policy, the End User License Agreement, and the Terms of Service Agreement;
      6. as required or authorized by law.
    4. AppVeyor collects statistics information (the " **Statistics** ") about projects, builds and technologies used for internal purposes. All Statistics are gathered in anonymous form without any relation to specific user or account. AppVeyor reserves the right to share Statistics with any third-party or post publicly.
  4. Use, Disclosure and Retention
    1. Personal Information is not collected, used or disclosed by AppVeyor for purposes other than those for which it was collected, except with your express consent or as required by law. AppVeyor will only disclose Personal Information about you to unrelated third-parties after you have been informed in advance of the possibility of such use and disclosure, and have consented to such disclosure. AppVeyor retains Personal Information for only as long as indicated in Section 3, above, or as required by law.
  5. Safeguards
    1. AppVeyor has developed procedures to safeguard your Personal Information. This includes protecting the access to, use, disclosure, retention and disposal of Personal Information. For more information, you can contact our Privacy Officer at [privacy@appveyor.com](mailto:privacy@appveyor.com).
  6. COMMUNITY SUPPORT
    1. In addition, AppVeyor provides public forums such as message boards, bulletin boards, discussion groups or chat rooms in the form of "community support", the terms of which are provided in the Terms of Service. As per our Terms of Service, you may not post any personal information on the public forum, including your name, address, email, website, or location.
  7. Links to Other Sites & Third-Party Content
    1. When you leave the Site, the privacy statements of the third-parties will apply. AppVeyor is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites. Should you find a link from any other website in Site that you feel is inappropriate, do not hesitate to contact us immediately.
  8. MORE INFORMATION
    1. Should you have any further questions or concerns about the privacy of information you provide to AppVeyor, please feel free to contact our Privacy Officer at: [privacy@appveyor.com](mailto:privacy@appveyor.com).
